http://www.olivemill.com/privacy.aspx

Home
Home
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology
that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy
applies to the Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County Web site and governs data collection and usage.
By using the Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County website, you consent to the data practices described
in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail
address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County also
collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as
your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically
collected by Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County. This information can include: your IP address,
browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This
information is used by Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County for the operation of the service, to
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use
of the Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information
or personally sensitive data through Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County public message boards,
this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County
does not read any of your private online communications.
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites
you choose to link to from Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County so that you can understand how those
Web sites collect, use and share your information. Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County is not responsible
for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County
and Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County collects and uses your personal information to operate the Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County
Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County also uses
your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services
available from Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County and its affiliates. Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County may also
contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services
or of potential new services that may be offered.
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business
partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases,
your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone
number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County
may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send
you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All
such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to
provide these services to Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County, and they are required to maintain
the confidentiality of your information.
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such
as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County, in order to determine what Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County services are
the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising
within Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested
in a particular subject area.
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice,
only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is
necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process
served on Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or
property of Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect
the personal safety of users of Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online
experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page
server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the
domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save
you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned
to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County pages, or
register with Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County site or services, a cookie helps Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County
to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process
of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses,
and so on. When you return to the same Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County Web site, the information
you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County
features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically
accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies
if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience
the interactive features of the Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County secures your personal information from unauthorized access,
use or disclosure. Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County secures the personally identifiable information
you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit
card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use
of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect
company and customer feedback. Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County encourages you to periodically
review this Statement to be informed of how Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County is protecting your
information.
Contact Information
Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy.
If you believe that Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County has not adhered to this Statement, please
contact Granite | Quartz | Corian | Porcelain Countertops - Kitchen Countertops. Anaheim, Orange County at andy@olivemill.com.
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the
problem.
